{"allRounds":[{"name":"Star Wars","timeLimitInSeconds":30,"pointsAddedForCorrectAnswer":10,"questions":[{"questionText":"In how many languages is C-3P0 fluent?","answers":[{"answerText":"4 Million","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"6 Thousand","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Over 10 Million","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Over 6 Million","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"What is the Wookiee's home world?","answers":[{"answerText":"Tatooine","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Kashyyyk","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Naboo","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Coruscant","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What does AT-AT stand for?","answers":[{"answerText":"Armored Tank Attack Transport","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Awesome Tall Attack Thing","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"A Trasport Attack Thing","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"All Terrain Armored Transport","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"What is the name of Boba Fett's ship?","answers":[{"answerText":"Centennial Falcon","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Slave 1","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Slave 2","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Death Star","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Who was the original commander of the Death Star?","answers":[{"answerText":"Grand Moff Tarkin","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Darth Vader","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Sheev Palpatine","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Boba Fett","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Lord Of The Rings","timeLimitInSeconds":45,"pointsAddedForCorrectAnswer":20,"questions":[{"questionText":"Who possesses the ring of power at the start of the Lord Of The Rings?","answers":[{"answerText":"Frodo","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Bilbo","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Sauron","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Gandalf","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Who do the hobbits encounter at the Prancing Pony?","answers":[{"answerText":"Gandalf","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Legolas","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Strider","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Boromir","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"How many members make up the fellowship of the ring?","answers":[{"answerText":"Ten","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Eight","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Nine","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Seven","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Who is the first member of the fellowship to be separated from the group?","answers":[{"answerText":"Legolas","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Boromir","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Aragorn","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Gandalf","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"What is the name of the capital of Gondor?","answers":[{"answerText":"Osgiliath","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Helm's Deep","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Minas Tirith","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Cirith Ungol","isCorrect":false}]}]}]}